## Wanfei (Felicia) Luo

Tel: 732-532-9054 Email: <a href="mailto:luowanfei@gmail.com">luowanfei@gmail.com</a> Website: <a href="https://felicia1017.github.io/#home">https://felicia1017.github.io/#home</a>

**SUMMARY:** Highly motivated, adaptable graduate student concentrated in Data Analytics with strong knowledge of analytical languages, such as Python (Pandas, Numpy, Seaborn, Scikit-Learn, Matplotlib, OpenCV EAST) R, SQL, and hands-on experience with AWS services (Redshift, S3, SageMaker), BusinessObjects, Oracle Database, and Tableau at work.

### **EDUCATION:**

Master of Business and Science Rutgers University, New Brunswick NJ Graduation: May 2020

• Concentration: Data Analytics

**Bachelor of Arts** Rutgers University, New Brunswick NJ Graduation: May 2018

Major: EconomicsMinor: Statistics

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

1-year Next-gen Data Analyst Intern Legg Mason, NYC, NY May 2019 to June 2020 American investment management firm with a focus on worldwide asset management services.

- Liaised between IT and product team to build an AWS Redshift-based enterprise database system and integrate external data and internal data for improving pipeline operations.
- Built new managerial dashboards on Tableau (SQL-based) by querying internal and competitive data from enterprise database and external sources to evaluate and monitor product performance.
- Collaborated stakeholders in Product for ad hoc reporting and fund net flow analytics using Python.
- Conducted monthly and quarterly reports on competitive pricing analysis using SAP BusinessObjects and excel for the US product team and fund board members.

Data Analyst Externship Becton Dickinson, Franklin Lake, NJ Sep 2018 to Feb 2019 Leading global provider of pharmaceutical devices and technology solutions.

- Cleaned 2-year text-based T&E (Travel and Expenses) data using python for text mining and data visualization.
- Conducted research and implemented ad hoc natural language processing analysis to help spot anomalous transactions using R.
- Visualized anomalous T&E transactions by utilizing large structured and unstructured datasets.

### SIGNIFICANT PROJECT

# DICOM Image Classification for Teleradiology

- Adopted deep learning based OpenCV East as the text extractor to capture the text locations and then created bounding boxes on each image.
- Implemented InceptionV3 as the pre-trained CNN model to identify ultrasound machine models. Implemented Multi-layer Perceptron as the classification algorithm structure to predict PII points.
- The end-to-end model achieved a highest accuracy score of 0.9740.

#### **ACHIEVEMENT / CERTIFICATION:**

- Treasurer, MBS student organization Jan 2019 to May 2020
- MBS Fellowship 2020 academic year
- National Swimming Championship 2011-2012 (China) silver medal in women's 100-meter butterfly